

karim Elsayd Sharf Eldin

② : Dubai ,United Arab Emirates

\(: (+971) 561423226

🚺 : https://karimsharaf55.github.io/UI-UX-Designer-Portfolio/

in : www.linkedin.com/in/karimsharaf55

Be: https://www.behance.net/karimsharf

About Me:

Highly Committed And Efficient Production. A Self-Sufficient, Hard Worker Who Is Highly Motivated And Very Personable . I Like To Learn A Lot About The Future Tools And Knowledge Which Is Affecting Our Modern World But Also Learn About History, That's I'm In The Learning Zone .

Languages

Arabic **Native**English **profesional**

Skills

Interaction Design

User Research

Design Strategy

User Interviews

Usability Testing

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Design System

User Interface Design

Rapid Prototyping

Tools& technologies

Figma

Adobe Xd

Sketch

Webflow

Zeplin

Understanding

HTML5 JavaScript/JQuery

CSS3/SASS GIT/Github

React Js 00P

PWA

Education

UI-UX Design @Route

Product Design @Route

Experience

UX/UI Design

Freelance | MAY 2022 - Present

- I created information architecture diagrams, wireframes, user journey maps, interactive prototypes, and high fidelity wireframes.
- Understand end-user requirements and create overall UX concept and strategy.
- interviewing users and conducted usability sessions to understand pain points with the product and communicating the UX strategy through our design criteria.

UX/UI Design Intern

Code Netro | SEP 2021 - FEB 2022

- During my internship, I worked closely with UX designers in designing products from scratch to hand off the design to the development team
- Generating advantage of user insights in the user research to identify the user behaviors.
- Researching on product features and user motivation factors and Using Ideation techniques to come up with solutions

Front-End Developer

Freelance | OCT 2018 - AUG 2021

- I collaborated with designers & developers to manage wide of projects from design to test and up to production.
- Implemented responsive cross-platform websites, mobile apps and landing pages from concept with my clients.